neurostechnology.com 2007-06-26

# Neuros: Privacy Policy

Neuros Audio, LLC ("Neuros") is committed to helping you make the most of your free time on the Internet within a trusted environment. This Privacy Policy discloses how we collect, protect, use and share information gathered about you on our web sites. We hope that this disclosure will help increase your confidence in our sites and enhance your experience on the Internet. 

**Questions**

What types of information do Neuros's web sites collect, and how are the sites collecting it?

How does Neuros use the personally identifiable information that has been collected?

Does Neuros share information with third party companies or other organizations?

What choices do I have about Neuros collecting, using, and sharing my information?

What type of security does Neuros provide?

How can I access my account information?

Whom do I contact with questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy?

**Answers**

**What types of information do Neuros's web sites collect, and how are the sites collecting it?**

The majority of information and services provided on our web sites are offered without our collecting any personally identifiable information from you. You can surf Neuros's web sites anonymously.

**Information You Provide**

There are a few activities on our web sites where the collection of personally identifiable information is necessary. Those activities include things like downloading software, making a purchase, entering a contest or sweepstakes, participating in our forums or contacting us. When personally identifiable information is collected, you will know because you will have to fill out a form. For most activities, we collect only your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, and zip code. When you make a purchase, we also collect your street and billing addresses, your phone number, and credit card information, if applicable. Personal information, including questions about your music interests, may also be collected for use by Neuros to improve the content of our web site, to customize the content and/or layout of our web site, to notify consumers about updates to our web site and/or to contact consumers for marketing purposes. 

**Information Collected from You with Technology**

 ****

Neuros web sites collect some information about you using technology, so it may not be readily apparent to you that it is being collected. For instance, when you come to our web site your IP address is collected so that we know where to send information you are requesting. An IP address is often associated with the place from which you enter the Internet like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. This information is not personally identifiable. Neuros web sites use information collected through technology to make our sites more interesting and useful to you. This includes helping advertisers on our site design advertisements you might like. We normally don't combine this type of information with personally identifiable information. However, we will combine this information with personally identifiable information to identify a visitor in order to enforce compliance with our Terms of Service or to protect our services, web sites, visitors, or others. 

**What Are Cookies, and How Does Neuros Use Them?**

Cookies are pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer while you are viewing the web site. These pieces of information allow the web site to remember important information that will make your use of that site more useful. Neuros and other Internet companies use cookies for a variety of purposes. For instance, our shopping areas on our web site use cookies to remember and process the items in your shopping cart. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many Neuros features that make your web experience more efficient, and some of our services will not function properly. 

**How does Neuros use the personally identifiable information that has been collected?**

Neuros uses personally identifiable information in a limited number of ways. We use the information to complete transactions. For instance, if you purchase products or software from our web site, we use your information to process your order, or if you contact us for help we will use the information to contact you. We use information collected to notify you if you've won a game or contest. Information we collect is used to send you e-mail updates and newsletters about our sites and products. We also use the information you provide to send you Neuros e-mail promotions and special offers from our third-party affiliates, partners and sponsors.

**Does Neuros share information with third party companies or other organizations?**

One of the most valuable assets of our business is you. We aren't in the business of selling information about our visitors. However, if we believe there is a value for our visitors, we will share your information or send you messages on behalf of another company as described below. We will also share information for security reasons. 

**Companies That Are "Standing in the Shoes" of Neuros**

Sometimes we hire companies to help us deliver products or services, like a shipping company that delivers a package. In those instances, we need to share your information with them. These companies are basically "standing in the shoes" of Neuros, and they are allowed to use the information only to deliver the product or service. 

**Companies Offering Promotions, Products, or Services**

On occasion, we may offer promotions -- like sweepstakes -- in conjunction with a sponsor. We will share your information with the sponsors if they need it to send you a product, such as a magazine subscription. We may share your information with those sponsors so that they can send you other special promotions they offer, but only if you give us your permission to do so, and we will share it only with that specific sponsor. In addition, Neuros occasionally sends e-mail promotions out to our visitors on behalf of third- party sponsors. In this instance, we don't share your name with the third party -- we do the mailing for them. Again, we only send these promotions to you if you've given your permission. 

**Content Partners**

On some of our sites, we may provide content that is created by a third-party partner web site. For instance, we may provide shopping opportunities with third parties. In some instances the third-party sites will collect information in order to facilitate the transaction or to make the use of their content more productive and efficient. In these circumstances the information collected is shared between Neuros and our third-party sponsors. 

**Third-Party Advertisers and Network Advertisers**

To help increase privacy protections for our visitors, Neuros allows advertising on our sites from only those companies that have their own privacy policy. Once you've clicked on an advertisement and have left Neuros's web sites, our Privacy Policy no longer applies. You must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their site. 

In addition, many business advertisements are managed and placed on our site by third- party companies. These companies are called "network advertisers." Network advertisers collect non-personally identifiable information when you click on or scan one of their banner advertisements. The information is collected using technology, so you may not realize it's being collected. The network advertisers collect this information so that they can show you ads that are more relevant and interesting to you. If you would like to read more about network advertisers or do not want network advertisers to collect this non-personally identifiable information about you, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

**Organizations That Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Guests and Our Sites**

We will give out personal information as required by law, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena, to enforce our Terms of Service or to protect the safety and security of our visitors and our web sites. 

**What choices do I have about Neuros collecting, using, and sharing my information?**

It is possible for you to use much of our web site without giving us any personally identifiable information. When you do register with us or give us personally identifiable information, you will have an opportunity at the time we collect your information to limit e-mail communications from Neuros and from our third-party partners. You can request at any time that Neuros not send future e-mail to you either by unsubscribing from the communication or by contacting us at unsubscribe@digitalinnovations.com. Also, as mentioned above, there are ways to limit the information collected through technology -- though some of our features won't work if you decide to do this.

**What type of security does Neuros provide?**

The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our visitors is of utmost concern to us. Neuros takes technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps to protect all visitors' information. When you provide credit card information, we use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to protect it. There are some things that you can do to help protect the security of your information as well. For instance, never give out your password, since this is what is used to access all of your account information. Also remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you finish surfing the Internet, so that other people using the same computer won't have access to your information.

**How can I access my account information?**

You can access the personally identifiable information you gave us during registration at customer profile. Simply login with your member name and password, and then click My Profile in the top right hand menu. There are instructions on the start page to help you recover your password if you've forgotten it. 

You can also contact us via e-mail. Please include information in the e-mail that will help us identify your account so we can assist you with your inquiry or request.

**Whom do I contact with questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy?**

If you need further assistance, please send an e-mail with your questions or comments to [info@digitalinnovations.com](mailto:info@digitalinnovations.com)

Or write us at: 

Neuros Audio, LLC  
650 W. Lake Street  
Suite 330  
Chicago, Illinois 60661  
Attention: Webmaster
